CURRICULUM VITAE

MARIUS PRUTEANU



PORTFOLIO

LANGUAGE

HORRIES

CONTACT

Profile

Programming is everything I love, being nerdy about creativity, problem solving and technology. With three years of experience as a technical analyst, Service Desk deputy team leader and ICT engineer, I am enthusiastic, self-taught, and keen to learn new programming skills and develop my career. In addition, my ex-military background taught me to be a responsible, team player, focused, versatile and multi-task-oriented person, able to adapt effectively to challenging situations. Currently, I am studying the OU Computer Science - BSc(Honours) Software development subject, year 2. Furthermore, I am currently looking for an entry-level developer position.

EDUCATION

Management:

organisational management, leadership, communication, time management, problem-solving, decision making, active listening, planning and customer service.

WORK EXPERIENCE

1st and 2nd line technical support, MS Office365 Admin, Azure admin, software installation, Incident Management, remote user support, SCCM, Active Directory, printers troubleshooting, mobile devices, kit installation, hardware replacement, OS age deployment, and application support.

Java 8, PowerShell, Phyton, HTML5, JavaScript, SQL, OOP principles, algorithms, data structures

PROFILE

Work Experience

SWP - ICT Technical Support Engineer

May 2022 to present

- Carry out, technical, investigative and/or administrative activities
- Carry out, technical, investigative and/or administrative activities
 To set up and operate associated machinery/equipment within specialist area
 Organise, schedule and attends events/meetings/resources, including equipment, people and systems as directed
 Co-ordinate with other teams members or members of other team from ICT department
 Assist in the interpretation of data, test resultsand present possible findings accurately and on time
 May require the installation of relevant software and re-calibrating of associated equipment
 Ensure full compliance with relevant regulations for designated areas of work

CGI - Service Desk Deputy Team Leader

November 2021 to May 2022

- ember 2021 to May 2022
 Coordinate the Service Desk team members in their daily duties of attending to clients who come to make inquiries and facilitate good customer service culture in team members
 Evaluate and assess service delivery performance metrics and carry out a survey on clients to weigh the level of service delivery in the company
 Keep a record of daily operations at the desk for tracking of customer needs, services rendered, and future reference
 Delegate specific service desk responsibilities to team members to create specialisation and increase service delivery pace
 Review all client complaints, rectify issues and liaise with appropriate departments to handle complex issues in a bid to provide more effective solutions

Graduation year

2004

2018

In progress (year 2)

CGI - Service Desk Analyst

June 2019 to November 2021

- 2019 to November 2021
 Log calls via the appropriate call logging system and provides a high level of technical fi
 To ensure that all is work carried out following ITIL Incident Management guidelines
 To achieve all team and personal performance goals as defined by the company
 DEnsure compliance to ISO9001(Quality), ISO14001 (Environmental), ISO27001 (Security), ISO22301 (Business Continuity) and BS18000 (Health and Safety) procedures
 Review all client complaints, rectify issues and liaise with appropriate departments to handle complex issues in a bid to provide more effective solutions

Subject

Computing and IT -Software

Bachelor of Management, RQF Level 6

Education University/Training body Open University ROU Military Land Forces Academy

Qualifications		
Course/Qualification name	Graduation year	Issued by
Object-oriented Java programming	2021	Open University
Secure Programmer: Intro to Programming Standards	2021	CGI e-learning platform
Blue Prism Foundation Training	2021	Blue Prism University
Software Development Concepts	2021	CGI e-learning platform
Network Essentials	2020	Cisco Network Academy
CompTIA+(220-901)	2019	CompTIA+
ITILv4 Foundation	2019	PeopleCERT
CompTIA IT Fundamentals FCO-U51	2019	CompTIA
Active Directory	2019	Microsoft Worldwide Learning

Introduction to Cybersecurity 0818 **Portfolio**

"Online Digital CV" Project

This online CV is part of my portfolio and was build in HTML5 language and external CSS3

Language

- English proficient French intermediate Romanian native speaker

Hobbies

- Ancient History Traveling
- Skydiving
- Spending time with my family

Cisco Network Academy

an.pruteanu@gmail.com LinkedIn Github